further.co.uk 2015-09-05

# Further.co.uk - Privacy Policy

###  To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

###  The information we collect 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Further website. On some pages, you can enter personal details, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: * Name * Email address * Date of birth (Optional)

Further runs competitions and promotions, in which instances you can submit extra information about yourself. For example, if you enter our monthly competition, you will need to submit your address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: * Name * Address * Postcode

###  The way we use information 

We use the information you provide about yourself when registering only to identify users of Further (To prevent abuse of the site). We do not share this information with outside parties except where demanded by court order or by law enforcement agencies.

We use the extra information you provide about your address when entering competitions/promotions only to ship the prize and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We do not store this information after the competition or promotion is over.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

We use your registered email address to send you our occasional newsletter, which contains news about the site, new features, and other information. We may also include some advertising in this newsletter, but to send adverts will never be the reason for any mailing. You can opt out of our newsletter via your ‘Your Account’ profile.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

###  Our commitment to data security 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

###  Our commitment to children's privacy: 

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

###  How To Contact Us 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email [info@further.co.uk](mailto:info@further.co.uk) Further Digital Marketing Limited is registered in England and Wales Company Number 06459835. Registered office: The Old Church, St Matthews Road, Norwich NR1 1SP.

###  Cookie Policy 

#### What Are Cookies

As is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience. This page describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade or ‘break’ certain elements of the sites functionality.

#### Disabling Cookies

You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser Help for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of the this site. Therefore it is recommended that you do not disable cookies.

#### Third Party Cookies

In some special cases we also use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this site.

This site uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solution on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content.

For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page.

#### How We Use Cookies

We use cookies for a variety of reasons detailed below. Unfortunately in most cases there are no industry standard options for disabling cookies without completely disabling the functionality and features they add to this site. It is recommended that you leave on all cookies if you are not sure whether you need them or not in case they are used to provide a service that you use.

#### The Cookies We Set

If you create an account with us then we will use cookies for the management of the signup process and general administration. These cookies will usually be deleted when you log out however in some cases they may remain afterwards to remember your site preferences when logged out.

We use cookies when you are logged in so that we can remember this fact. This prevents you from having to log in every single time you visit a new page. These cookies are typically removed or cleared when you log out to ensure that you can only access restricted features and areas when logged in.
